紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   窩車則髡賊
翻譯   肉松
翻譯   Lynn_寧
翻譯   杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯   鹽湖涼開水
時間軸   知之。
后期   餓得慌
校對  草草
顧問  老杜
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第六季  第七集
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
弗·安  第一章
我們眾志成城
女性平等
就是人人平等
新全國女性會議
道·斯
謝潑德堂
舞蹈中心
鄧肯·謝潑德
回應應用軟件讀取隱私信息的指控
你到底殺沒殺瑞秋
Did you kill Rachel?
是我殺的
I did.
但你找不到她的
But you won't find her.
沒人能找得到
No one will.
我很榮幸能成為繼任大法官候選人
I am deeply honored to be considered for the late Justice's seat.
他們怎么買通你的  謝潑德家族
How did they buy you? The Shepherds.
布雷特·科爾將成為議長
Brett Cole will be the speaker.
如果不算馬克  他就是下一個總統繼任者
Next in line, if you don't count Mark.
我們得把那女人趕下臺
We've gotta get this woman outta there!
你有沒有利用阿卡斯泄漏事件
Did you use the Arcas accident
慫恿貝爾波特居民注冊一款應用
to get the citizens of Bellport to sign up for this app?
你協助謝潑德自由基金
An app that you helped develop
開發出來的應用
for the Shepherd Freedom Foundation?
弗蘭西斯是個不擇手段的人
Francis was a desperate man.
但不管他做了什么  都是他自己做的
But whatever he did, he did alone.
我都沒有參與
I was not complicit.
我想我們最好還是在正式場合談一談
I think it's best if we meet under more formal circumstances.
錄音采訪
And on the record.
那你為什么沒有合法收養我
Why didn't you legally adopt me?
他不是咱家的人
He's not one of us.
你個孬種
You're a coward.
我希望你快死
Well, I hope you die.
他給你的最后一樣東西
The last thing he gave you.
我倒希望你能告訴我是什么意思  克萊爾
I was kind of hoping you could tell me, Claire.
湯姆·哈默施密特死了
Tom Hammerschmidt is dead.
還有凱茜  簡
Cathy, Jane.
比爾·謝潑德也要去蹲監獄了
Bill Shepherd is going to prison.
馬克已經四面楚歌
Mark has no one to turn to.
只有你和我了
It's just you and me.
上帝保佑  弗蘭西斯和我有孩子了
Francis and I have been blessed.
痛苦分兩種
There are two kinds of pain.
一種讓你變得更強
The sort of pain that makes you strong.
另一種毫無價值
Or useless pain...
只是徒添折磨
the sort of pain that's only suffering.
我對沒價值的東西也沒耐心
I have no patience for useless things.
我回頭望向她
I turn around and see her,
我親愛的妻子  倚靠在前廊上
my darling wife, poised on the front stoop.
她肯定都看見了
Surely she saw everything.
所有的殺戮  相關的謊言  但她未置一詞
The killing, the lying about it, but doesn't say a word.
她只是若無其事地回到房子里
She just enters the house in quiet compliance.
這就是愛
This is love.
每個人都應該
Everyone should be so--
我親愛的同胞們
My beloved Americans.
我現在百感交集
My heart is very full today.
我今天來談談未來
I am here to talk about the future.
未來已經變得極度私人化
And the future has become very personal.
我們聚集在偉大祖國的中心
We are gathered here at the very center of our great nation
來慶祝這個歷史性的女性集會
to celebrate this historic Women's Conference.
這一刻對于美國人民影響深遠
This is a profound moment for all Americans.
但這也是危險的時刻  朋友們
But it's also a perilous time in our history, my friends.
因為一些國內的寡頭們
Because the American oligarchs out there,
正對我們虎視眈眈
they are coming for us.
他們正試圖剝奪憲法賦予我的
They are trying to strip me of my constitutional power
身為三軍統帥的權力
as your Commander In Chief.
下級法院作出了對我有利的判決
Now the lower court ruled in my favor,
但他們正要把此案
but now they've taken this case
上訴至最高法院
all the way to the Supreme Court.
他們要把我的手指從核按鈕上挪開
And they want my finger off the nuclear button.
我想問問
And I have to ask...
你覺得他們為什么要這樣
Why do you think that is?
這些寡頭
These oligarchs,
通過一個看似無害的應用
through an innocent seeming app,
正試圖通過偷窺你的手機
have been trying to steal the midterms
侵犯你的隱私
by crawling your phones,
指揮你如何投票
invading your privacy
來竊取中期選舉的勝利
and telling you how to vote.
那么  你會讓他們為所欲為嗎
Now, are you gonna let them get away with it?
不
No!
我們得讓他們清醒過來
We need to tell them to wake up!
跟著我一起說  堪薩斯州黎巴嫩的民眾
Say it with me, Lebanon, Kansas.
國會應該
It is time for Congress to...
醒醒了
Wake up!
最高法院應該
And it's time for the Supreme Court to...
醒醒了
Wake up!
我的目標是讓美國更上一層樓
Now, my purpose is to elevate America,
為她奮斗
fight for America,
如果有必要的話  為她犧牲
and if it ever came to it, die for America.
我會成為大家的父親  母親  領袖以及朋友
I will be father, mother, leader and friend.
非常感謝
Thank you so much.
父親  母親  領袖
Father, mother, leader...
騙子  殺手
liar, killer.
安息吧  瑞秋
Rest in peace, Rachel.
這是什么時候的錄像
When's the footage from?
幾天前的
It's from several days ago.
他一直待在一個小屋里
He's been staying at a cabin.
他小時候住過的地方  待了三四周
Childhood cabin for three or four weeks.
我們懷疑他潛藏在洛賽瑞歐斯外的山里
We suspect he's in the mountains outside Los Cerillos now.
他找到埋她尸體的地方了嗎
And did he find where he buried her?
我們還不確定
We're still not sure.
女士  我收到一名前探員的爆料
Ma'am, I got a tip from a former agent.
他曾受謝潑德兄妹指使去加夫尼打探
One of the ones poking around Gaffney on behalf of the Shepherds.
道格最近聯系了賽斯·格雷森
Doug recently reached out to Seth Grayson.
我們知道他們談了什么嗎
Do we know what was discussed?
不  但這是你上次和他談話后
No, but it's the first time he's contacted
他第一次與謝潑德家族
anyone connected with the Shepherds
有關的人聯絡
since you last spoke to him.
如果他這么想被抓的話  那就抓住他
Well, if he's trying to get caught, let's catch him.
鄧肯·謝潑德到底會不會去作證
So is Duncan Shepherd testifying or not?
他的律師還在談條件
His lawyers are negotiating the terms.
他們希望他能不公開作證
They're hoping that he could meet behind closed doors.
那他必須得被傳喚
Well, then he needs to be subpoenaed.
我們會見過的每個議員
Every congressperson we've spoken to
-都同意如此  但是  -他們在拖延
- agrees he should be and yet-- - They're delaying.
他們并不真想
I mean, there's no real desire
推動針對應用的調查
to move this app investigation along.
他們想保護自己人
They're protecting their own.
是眾議院要求舉行聽證會的
The House asked for these hearings.
他們需要走過場
The theatre is good for them.
但我們在跟委員會的
But we are in constant contact
民主黨成員密切聯系  女士
with the Democratic members of the committee, ma'am.
給他們壓力
They're feeling the pressure.
顯然壓力還不夠
Well, clearly, not enough.
我們可以先逮捕幾個議員
We can start arresting congresspeople.
有必要的話  把他們從眾議院拉出來
Pull them out of the chambers if we have to.
-舉行聽證會的意義  -是什么  打太極嗎
- The whole point of the hearings-- - Is what? Obfuscation?
怎么  這可是侵犯隱私的事
What? We're talking about invasion of privacy here.
聯邦檢察官要證據確鑿才肯
The US Attorney is resistant to pressing any kind of charges
-提出訴訟  -應用本身就是確鑿證據
- without hard evidence. - The app is the evidence.
-這就是起訴理由  諾拉  -也許吧
- This is grounds for prosecution, Nora. - Yes, maybe.
但聯邦檢察官不會同意
But the US Attorney would argue--
那就換掉聯邦檢察官
Replace the US Attorney.
這件事她拖了好幾個月了
She's been dragging her feet on this for months.
女士  我們還得走正當程序
Ma'am, we still live in a world of due process.
這會發出令人不安的信號
That would send a chilling message--
我們需要發出保護民主的信號
The message is we need to protect our democracy.
出于實際考慮  我們要取消今天的第四站行程
On a practical note, we're canceling the fourth stop today.
我們斟酌后覺得去了克利夫蘭就不用去托萊多了
Upon reflection, we decided Toledo would be redundant with Cleveland.
帕姆  沒事  不妨直說
Pam, it's fine. You can be honest.
三軍統帥
The Commander In Chief
今天有些迷糊而已
is feeling a little woozy today. That's all.
而且還有點暴躁  但沒什么的  真的
And yes, maybe a little cranky, but nothing serious. I promise.
我們一到得梅因
When we touch down in Des Moines,
諾拉  你就可以直接回華府了
Nora, you can head straight back to DC.
斯克斯基  你是斯拉夫人嗎
Is it Slavic, "Skorsky"?
我是波蘭裔
Polish, in my case.
你很孤獨吧
You must be lonely.
我讓記者團乘第二架飛機
I asked the press corps to take the second plane,
我們就好私下見面
so that you and I could meet privately.
四個月前  你見了兩個人
Four months ago, you met with two people.
現在一個人失蹤了  一個人死了
One of them's missing and one of them is dead.
我最近總是遇到不幸
My life has certainly been punctuated with loss lately.
但也有運氣
And just a bit of great luck.
但湯姆·漢默施密特就不走運了
Tom Hammerschmidt was not lucky.
沒錯  確實很悲慘
No, he wasn't. That was tragic.
所以我覺得你該繼承他的衣缽
That's why I think you should pick up his mantle.
完整地講述弗蘭西斯的政治生涯
And tell the full story of Francis' political career.
你在逗我嗎
Are you messing with me?
不  我說真的
No. Far from it.
你調查并曝光了謝潑德自由基金會
You did a great job investigating and exposing
應用的事  這非常出色
the Shepherd Freedom Foundation app.
曝光其非法用途
Its nefarious uses.
我們不能讓議員逍遙法外
We can't let congresspeople get away with things like that.
我懷疑最高法院廢了你之前
I wonder if you'll get them in line
你能不能控制住他們
before the Supreme Court takes your power away.
我和湯姆·漢默施密特最后一次談話時
Tom Hammerschmidt and I, the last time we spoke,
談到了我丈夫
we talked about my husband.
我希望可以跟你說完
And my hope is I could pick it up with you.
我有很多關于弗蘭西斯的事要說
I have a lot that needs to be said about Francis,
他大大小小的罪過
his crimes and misdemeanors.
你想不想聽我說
You want my story or don't you?
又是輕微宮縮
Oh, it's these mini contractions.
這叫希克斯假陣縮
They're, um... called Braxton Hicks.
你有孩子嗎
Do you have kids?
沒有
No, I don't.
這胎兒動靜真大
Oh, the baby's really moving now.
寶寶在踢  你想摸摸看嗎
It's kicking. Do you want to feel?
不用了  謝謝
No, thank you.
這感覺真奇妙
Such a strange feeling.
要對另一個生命負責
To be wholly responsible for the life of another.
我還聽說  等你有了孩子
Also, I hear, when you have kids, you never...
就沒法像以前一樣睡覺了
sleep quite the same again.
痛苦分兩種
There are two kinds of pain.
道格·斯坦普給我發了條信息
Doug Stamper sent me that text,
他說這是你丈夫日記里的話
he said it comes from your husband's diary.
我要問你
Now, I ask you,
我該采訪你  還是他
who should I interview, you or him?
我知道你們有些人過來
I know that some of you are here
是因為不確定
because you're not sure
明年的聚會我是否還會健在
I'm gonna be around at next year's gathering.
沒事  我從你們的表情里
Oh, no, no, I can see it on--
看得出  沒錯
On your faces. And it's true.
過去幾個月  我反思了一下
These last few months, I've had to look back.
但我很興奮  真的
But I'm excited. I am.
正如我妹妹所言
As my sister told you,
這個國家接下來幾個月會迎來改變
there are changes coming to this country in the next few months.
我為之努力了20多年
The kind that I haven't been able to accomplish
依然沒有實現
in the 20 plus years that I've been at it.
為人們去監管  給每個人一個機會
It'll cut regulation for the people, give every man a chance.
你授人以漁
You lead a man to fish, and he--
卻可能為此身陷囹圄  那就來吧
You want to lock me up in prison for that, then so be it, but...
還凍結我的資產
Seize my assets.
你們知道嗎
Did you read...
雀鳥也做夢
finches dream?
是啊
Yeah, yeah.
它們可以
They can-- They have the--
它們可以在入睡時為自己歌唱
They can sing to themselves when they sleep.
我說到哪兒了
Where was I?
我這邊有些議員想要退出
I have congressmen who want to break away.
從這件事里脫身
Separate themselves from this.
見風使舵嘛
Well, deflect and compliment.
這就是我在國會時的生存之道
That's how I survived the Hill.
這些聽證會會讓我們完蛋的  馬克
These hearings will blow up on us, Mark.
不管怎樣  我們都用過那個破應用
Now, one way or another, we all used that motherfucking app.
他們確實對我們不錯
And yes, they've been good to us, but...
但是我們憑什么要為那小子犯的錯買單
why do we all have to pay for what the son set in motion?
你對鄧肯有意見
Anything you want to say about Duncan,
跟安奈特說去
you say it to Annette.
我在請求你去說
Well, I'm asking you to say it.
時隔這么多年  真不敢相信
I can't believe I'm looking to you
我又再次向你求助
for help again all these years later.
你曾是副總統
You were vice president.
我東山再起了至少三次  布雷特
I've rebuilt my career at least three times, Brett.
有必要的話我還能卷土重來
And I will continue to do so as long as I have to.
可惜簡·戴維斯沒這個機會了
Too bad Jane Davis won't have that chance.
"我在克萊爾和佐伊面前是不同的人"
"What I am to Claire is not what I am to Zoe."
你明白這句話的意思嗎
Do you know what it means?
他覺得你能明白嗎
Does he believe you should know what it means?
是的  他補充道  "這是他留給我的"
Yes. He added, "And that's what he left me..."
這是弗蘭西斯日記上的話
It belongs to some diary that Francis kept.
但不是來自他的總統文件嗎
But not part of his presidential papers?
不管是什么  安德伍德總統
Whatever it is, it's information that President Underwood--
黑爾總統都不希望它曝光
President Hale wants kept out of the light.
道格暗示她為了
Doug implied that she got pregnant
奪去本屬于他的東西而懷上孕
so as to keep him from what was rightfully his.
你接下來什么時候能跟他通話
When will you speak with him next?
我猜是他下次找到公用電話或是一次性手機的時候
My guess is the next time he finds a payphone or a burner.
我要見他
I'd like to meet with him.
-安奈特  -你會出名的  布雷特
- Annette. - You're going to be famous, Brett.
出名也分美名遠揚
Well, there's fame...
和臭名昭著
and then there's notoriety.
你幾個月前簽署的法案
The bill you had your name on all those months ago...
會得到最高法院的支持
will be upheld in the Supreme Court.
這是阿布魯佐法官的多數判決
This is Judge Abruzzo's majority ruling.
-你怎么...  -是我們幫他寫的
- How did you-- - We helped him write it.
這個判決措辭犀利
It's worded in such a way
她的權力將會被慢慢地
that her powers will be diminished...
全部瓦解掉
over time and across the board.
馬克告訴你我們的計劃了嗎
Mark gave you a sense of what we're thinking?
說了一點
A bit.
你只需要拖延這些聽證會
You just need to run out the clock on these hearings.
中期選舉之后  你就可以強勢出手了
After the midterms, you can send a powerful message.
這些年我們有幸
Over the years, we've been lucky enough
扶持了一批富有才華
to support an array of talented
與我們志同道合的政治家
and like-minded politicians.
我們就像第三黨一樣
We've essentially operated like a third party.
總有一天
And one day,
在不遠的將來  我們會正式成立黨派
in the not too distant future, we'll make it official.
布雷特  你將成為黨的領袖
Brett, you will be the leader of that party.
你會入主白宮
You'll be our man in the White House.
我向布雷特表達了我們
I told Brett how thankful we are
對于他讓鄧肯免受媒體關注的謝意
for keeping Duncan out of the spotlight.
我不會忘記你為他做的事
I won't forget all you've done for him.
事實上  那是個很好的問題  鮑勃
Well, that's actually a very good question, Bob.
我們國家在世界上排名如何
Where do we rank as a country in the world?
如果你非要問的話  我們排第17
You have to ask that. We're 17.
這就是我們  第17
That's where we are. 17th.
-這簡直是恥辱  -說到恥辱
- That is a disgrace-- - Speaking of disgrace,
我有個問題問你  先生
I have a question for you, sir.
你生病是因為你家族的
Did your family make you sick
化學工廠和有毒地區嗎
with their chemical plants and their toxic sites?
把她帶出去
Get her out of here.
你是自作自受
You made yourself sick.
你會害死我們所有人
And you're killing all of us.
-來人把這位小姐帶出去  -當然了
- Somebody take care of this young lady. - Of course
他要趕我出去  你正在害死我們所有人
he's going to take me out. He is. You're killing all of us.
"我不打算說假話  我討厭小孩
"I'm not gonna lie, I despise children.
我就這么說了"
There, I've said it."
你搞什么鬼
What the hell is wrong with you?
"30分鐘前  佐伊給我發了條短信
"Thirty minutes ago I received a text from Zoe.
毫無疑問  她想道歉"
She intends to apologize, no doubt."
等等  等等  這話是哪來的
Wait, wait, what's that from?
我不是在說嗎
That's what I'm saying.
道格  來我這里  我們見一面
Doug, come here. Let's meet.
"誰都不聽話
"Rebellion on all fronts--"
克萊爾  佐伊  羅素  我不能失去決心"
"Claire, Zoe, Russo. I must not lose my resolve."
別說了  你在哪
Hey, stop. Where are you?
不  不  不  那是行不通的
No, no, no. That's not how this is gonna work.
道格  我們能找到你
Doug, we can find you.
用不了多久
It won't take very long.
我現在就告訴你我在哪
I'll tell you where I am right now.
就在一個鳥不拉屎的地方
Right in the middle of nowhere.
我五分鐘后就會離開這里  我要受不了了
I'm five minutes from out of here and out of fucking mind.
她只是想和你坐下談談
She just wants to sit with you.
我會告訴你我想讓什么被說出來和怎么說
I'm going to tell you what I want said and how.
他們有律師  有錢  我沒有
They have the lawyers, the money. I don't.
他們按我說的做
They do what I tell them,
那我們就可以見面
then I know we can meet.
你的要求都會得到滿足的  我保證
You will get everything that you are due. I'll make sure of it.
你什么時候再聯系我
When will I hear from you again?
抱歉他們把你叫到飛機上來  拉森醫生
I'm so sorry that they called you onto the plane, Dr. Larson.
我現在感覺好多了
I feel fine now.
但是依你現在的情況
All the same, you're getting close to a time
對你和孩子來說  飛來飛去可不是很好
where jumping on and off a plane may not be the best idea.
你說你覺得很累
You said you'd been feeling run down.
是的  有點  但...
Yes, a little bit. But--
我認為我們應該回華府
I think we should get you back to DC
驗一下血  以防萬一
to do some blood work as a precaution.
好  可以
Okay, that's fine.
但如果沒有威脅到孩子的安全
But unless I'm putting the baby in danger,
我今天還得再去兩個地方
I've got two more appearances today.
我建議你不要這么做
I'd advise against that.
我不能做請病假的總統  拉森醫生
I cannot be the indisposed president, Dr. Larson.
我相信你沒什么問題
I'm sure you're fine,
但是你的化驗結果顯示你有點脫水
but your sample tells me you're a bit dehydrated.
至少讓我給你輸點液
At least let me get you on an IV.
用不了多長時間的
It won't take long.
能讓你的體液回到正常水平
We'll get your fluids back to normal.
這真的有必要嗎
Is this really necessary?
他是個成年人了
He's a grown man.
如果你更愿意讓賽斯
If you'd rather have Seth
把簽好的文件拿給我  那也可以
bring me the signed documents that's fine, too.
安妮  你得承認
Annie, you have to admit
-這真是太荒謬了  -那是爸會說的話
- this is the most cockamamie thing-- - That's Dad's word.
還有拜托別把我當成
And please don't confuse me with someone
愿意繼續聽你的狗屁意見的人
who's willing to listen to one more of your goddamn opinions.
我們都要合法收養他
Each of us will legally adopt him.
等我們死了  就是鄧肯...
And when we're dead and gone, it will be Duncan...
繼承掌管
who is the face, voice and embodiment
謝潑德無限責任公司
of Shepherd Unlimited.
我是為你這么做的
I'm doing this for you.
-我要遲到了  -我在簽了
- I'm late. - I'm signing.
你想繼續避開我嗎
Is it your plan to keep avoiding me?
-比爾  -天啊  我到底怎么你了
- Bill. - Lordy, what exactly is it I did to you?
你覺得你知道什么是對我最好的
You think you know what's best for me.
我不是我們的父親
I am not our father.
如果你早點意識到這點多好
Would have been swell if you'd realized that sooner.
很高興你能和你的朋友
So glad you got to spend some time
度過如此美好的時光  比爾
with your friends like this, Bill.
我沒法不去想那個女人
I can't get that woman out of my head.
你覺得她說的對嗎
Do you think she was right?
我們害了自己
Did we poison ourselves?
阿布佐可以被彈劾嗎  是的
Is Abruzzo impeachable? Yes.
參議院會定他的罪嗎
Would the Senate convict him?
誰知道呢
Who knows?
但又有什么關系呢
But what does it matter?
你需要讓他害怕  這個辦法可能有用
You need him scared, and this might do it.
他在裁定一件
He received an interest-free loan
涉及謝潑德某子公司的案子時
from a Shepherd-owned entity
從謝潑德旗下的另一家機構
for a lake house at the same time
獲得了用于買湖邊別墅的
that he was ruling on a case that involved
無息貸款
another part of that company.
你沒事吧
Is everything all right?
沒事  抱歉  我只是有點脫水
Yes. Sorry. I'm just a little bit dehydrated.
為什么之前沒人說起過這件事  沃爾特
Why hasn't this ever come up before, Walter?
阿布佐并未被全面審查過
Abruzzo was never fully-vetted.
你  任何人都沒全面審查過他
By you, by anybody.
從某種程度上講  他被這樣強推上位
In a way, the fact that he was railroaded through
恰好為你提供了機會
has proved to be your opportunity.
最高法院的其他人呢
And the rest of the court?
板上釘釘了
Locked in.
阿布魯佐是搖擺票
Abruzzo's the swing vote.
謝潑德自由基金會
We at the Shepherd Freedom Foundation,
自由是關鍵詞
freedom being the operative word there,
堅信個人主義
believe in the individual.
可以說  我們基金會的理念
I could argue that our foundation is
比那些所謂的進步議程
more inclusive, more forward-looking
更具包容性和前瞻性
than any so-called progressive agenda.
聽啊
Oh, listen.
聽聽你們的聲音  你們全被洗腦了
Listen to you. You are so programmed
以至聽不進我的觀點
that you can't hear my argument.
納森  我也想幫你
Nathan. I wish I could help you.
在正在進行的調查中
Withholding information from
隱瞞證據可是犯罪
an ongoing investigation is a crime.
如果你知道他的所在
If you know anything about his whereabouts,
我建議你向我坦白
suggest you tell me.
這一切都結束后你準備做什么
What are you gonna do when all this is over?
你好好想想
I mean, think about it.
再過多久你會變成
How long before you become
那個掌握了太多秘密的人
the one with too many secrets?
我們的總統讓我害怕
Our president scares me.
如果還有誰清楚她的勾當  那就是你了
If anyone knows what she's been up to, it's you.
你還有孩子  對吧
You have children, right?
結過幾次婚
How many wives?
別把我的家人牽扯進來
Leave them out of it.
你能做到嗎
Can you?
我父親是名警察
My father was a cop.
我媽媽是名寡婦
My mom's a widow.
世道艱難  納森
It's a hard life, Nathan.
在局里待了這么多年
All those years at the Bureau.
你投入的時間  那些經驗  這都是很寶貴的
The time you put in, all that experience, it's valuable.
道格在哪里
Where's Doug?
這些活動有個特點
The thing about these events,
到處都是攝像頭
there's cameras everywhere.
賽斯
Seth.
別想岔  下面我要轉向攝像頭
No, because this is where I turn to the camera.
說一句
And I say,
我不知道
I don't know.
我很遺憾  但是有一家俄羅斯水軍公司
I'm sad to say, but there is a Russian troll factory
正在詆毀你丈夫的成就
that has begun to manipulate your husband's accomplishments.
那太糟糕了
That's awful.
不  我們抓到他們了  但是
No. We caught them. But for instance,
他在哈佛上學的記錄  他在桑蒂諾學院的記錄
records of his years at Harvard, his years at the Sentinel,
都幾乎查不到了
are virtually impossible to track down.
而是只有針對他的誹謗
Now, instead you find fabrications about him.
這么說吧  他們搞得烏煙瘴氣的
They filled the air with noise, so to speak.
我們上次會面時  你就擔心
I know from last we spoke, you were concerned
會出現這樣的局面
something like this could happen.
是的
Well, I was.
有人跟我說過這樣的可能性
That someone had mentioned the possibility to me.
但是我沒想到會成真
But I had no idea it could be done.
很不幸我們已經進入了新時代
We have unfortunately entered an era
數碼事實很容易被歪曲
where our digital truths are vulnerable.
這樣的話
In that case,
這些網絡水軍也能夸大我丈夫的罪行吧
couldn't these trolls amplify my husband's crimes as well?
沒錯
Yes.
這些言論的影響將很難消除
And those would be very difficult stories to take back.
維克多  如果真是如此那就太糟糕了
Viktor, that would be terrible if that were to happen.
如今的歷史由出價最高者書寫
History belongs to the highest bidder now.
希望后人記住的不會只是他的罪行
Well, I hope his reputation can survive his crimes.
我還希望
And I hope--
不  現在可不行
No, no, no, no, no, no, not now.
克萊爾  出什么問題了
Claire, something wrong?
-她怎么樣了  -心跳過快
- How's she doing? - She's tachycardiac
呼吸急促  Q5級宮縮
with elevated respirations, Q5 contractions.
你已經懷孕26周了  總統女士
You're 26 weeks pregnant, Madam President.
我們需要給她打4克含鎂注射液  開始靜脈點滴
We need to give her four grams of mag. Start the drip.
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
Francis Underwood?
Francis Underwood.
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
Francis Underwood?
你為什么要這么說他的名字
Why do you say his name like that?
你為什么要跟他訂婚
Why would you get engaged?
我沒訂婚
I'm not engaged.
-格雷琴說  -格雷琴應該少管閑事
- Gretchen said-- - Gretchen should mind her own business.
我還沒答應他
I haven't answered him yet.
跟他做愛肯定不怎么樣
The sex can't be great with him,
事實如此
it just can't.
和你做愛感覺很棒
The sex is great with you.
我還以為我們會日遍歐洲
I thought we were gonna fuck our way across Europe
中國  還有非洲什么的
and China and Africa or wherever.
誰說我們不會了
Who says we won't?
天殺的弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
Francis fucking Underwood.
里德  別鬧了好嗎
Reed. Would you stop?
拜托  他根本不是你喜歡的類型
I mean, come on. The guy's not your type.
那你就是
Oh, because you are?
你父母喜歡我
I'm your parents' type.
但如果他們真了解我  就不會喜歡我了
But I wouldn't be if they really knew me.
這就等于"是"了吧
Which I guess is another way of saying yes.
我就是你喜歡的類型
I am your type.
弗蘭西斯是動物的守護神
Francis is the patron saint of animals.
他總是說個沒完
He never stops talking.
我每次見到那家伙  他都在滔滔不絕
Every time I see that guy, his mouth is running.
因為他總有聽眾
Because he always has an audience
你永遠料不到他要說什么
and you never know what he's going to say.
克萊爾·黑爾
Claire Hale.
你想要什么
What do you want?
什么
What?
我要...
I want...
每扇門都大敞開
every door to be wide open
一直敞開
and stay that way.
那就給他打電話
Then call him...
說你跟他結束了  因為你要跟我走
and tell him it's over, because you're coming with me.
是嗎
I am?
弗蘭西斯  是我
Hi, Francis, it's me.
我五分鐘之后到
I'm five minutes away.
得有人把事情查清楚  總統女士
Someone will have to get to the bottom of it, Madam President.
我是說
I mean...
催產素能誘發分娩
Pitocin induces labor.
她再也別想執業了
She'll never practice again.
孩子會沒事的吧
Is the baby gonna be okay?
孩子沒事
The baby is fine.
你看
Here we go.
你想知道性別嗎
Would you like to know the sex?
喂
Hello.
臭婊子  是女孩
You fucking cunt. It's a girl.
我來找你了  克萊爾
I'm coming for you, Claire.
我不會逃跑的  納森
I'm not gonna run, Nathan.
北緯35度28分22秒
35 degrees, 28 minutes, 22 seconds north,
西經106度8分58秒
by a 106 degrees, 8 minutes, 58 seconds west.
你說什么呢
What are you talking about?
瑞秋·波斯納就埋在那里
It's where Rachel Posner is buried.
我問你  納森
Let me ask you something, Nathan.
經過這么長時間
After all this time.
經過這么多年  我們一起為弗蘭克做的一切
All these years together. Everything that we did for Frank.
盧卡斯
Stuff with Lucas,
麥卡倫
Macallan,
搞恐襲的那小子
the terrorist kid.
我們做的一切
Everything we ever did.
你真的要說  你要選她嗎
Are you seriously telling me, you're gonna choose her?
其實  我只關心能全身而退
Literally, all I care about is getting out of this alive.
上車
Get in.
怎么可能還沒找到他
How is it possible we still haven't found him?
上次有人看見他
Last time anybody saw him,
他在新墨西哥的邊境檢查站附近
he was in New Mexico near a border checkpoint.
你真相信他出國了
You honestly believe he's out of the country?
說不通  納森  逃跑不是他的作風
It just doesn't fit, Nathan. It's not like him to leave.
他最后一次和謝潑德兄妹聯系是什么時候
When's the last time he had contact with the Shepherds?
他似乎確實又向格雷森先生轉述了一些奇怪的話
I gather he did convey a few more curious quotes to Mr. Grayson.
但現在  他的話
But at this point, the feeling is
似乎更像是瘋子的胡話
they're like the ravings of a crazy person.
之后再談
We'll speak later.
他怎么...
How did he get--
不不不  寶貝
Oh, no, no, no, sweetheart.
你父親的苦果
I will not reap...
不會由我來收
what your father has sown.
沒事吧  總統女士
Is everything all right, Madam President?
沒事
Yes.
我在找東西
I was just looking for something.
女士  科爾議員來了
Ma'am, Congressman Cole's here.
要請他進來嗎
Shall I send him in?
好
Yes.
-總統女士  -布雷特
- Madam President. - Brett.
我想請你幫個忙
I wonder if you would do me a favor.
喬治·華盛頓的畫像
The George Washington painting.
可以幫我掛回壁爐上嗎
Would you mind hanging that back up over the mantle?
當然
No.
非常感謝  也謝謝你能來
Thank you so much and thank you for coming.
請坐
Please have a seat.
謝潑德兄妹是從什么時候開始支持你的
Now, the Shepherds started backing you when?
是在你和那個可憐女子的出軌悲劇
Was that during or after your tragic affair
發生時  還是之后
with the poor young woman?
我妻子知道我出軌
My wife knows about the affair.
-我沒法預知...  -別慌
- There was no way I could have predicted-- - Don't worry.
我沒打算利用那個污點對付你
I wasn't planning on using that nasty little piece of business.
我只想估計一下還要多久
I just wanted to gauge how long this was going to take.
先不談參議院
So, putting the Senate aside,
眾議院有多少人在用那個應用
how many members of the House were using that app?
說個近似數就行
Ballpark figure is fine.
司法聽證會就正在調查人數
That's what our judiciary hearings are trying to determine.
如有必要  我會直接逮捕
I'll go straight to arrests if I have to.
這是叛國  布雷特
This is treason, Brett.
會有人因此垮臺的
Somebody will go down for it.
那真正的問題就是  你會嗎
So, I guess the real question is will you?
因為我知道  這房間里  你努力想坐的椅子
Because I know the chair in this room that you're gunning for
并不是你的屁股現在坐的那把
is not the one your ass is currently warming.
原諒我的用語
Forgive me.
懷孕讓我變得粗俗了
I think pregnancy has brought out the sailor in me.
那么
So.
等這次會面結束
What you're going to say to the press
你要和媒體怎么說
as soon as this meeting is over.
你要說  你要求見我
You're going to say that you asked to meet with me
是為了匯報你最近注意到的一些
so that you could report some good old-fashioned quid pro quo
屢見不鮮的等價交易
that came to your attention.
我最近任命的最高法院法官
That my recent Supreme Court appointee
曾為了湖邊別墅而做出了偏私的裁決
was found trading a favorable ruling for a lake house.
令人震驚
Shocking.
你我都清楚
And that you and I both knew
那樣的話  你只能
that the only choice you then had
去國會  啟動...
was to go to congress and initiate--
從未有最高法院法官被彈劾過
No Supreme Court justice has ever been impeached.
那這位阿布佐法官
The good Justice Abruzzo
肯定不想成為第一個  對吧
wouldn't want to be the first then, would he?
阿布佐法官
Justice Abruzzo...
是黑人
is black.
那就讓這件事更...
Which makes this all the more--
又說到這個詞了  悲劇
There's that word again, tragic.
總統女士
Madam President.
你先別跟我說  我們不該見面
Before you explain to me how we shouldn't be meeting
或者布雷特不該在這里
or how Brett shouldn't be here,
三權分立等等
separation of branches and all that.
我們正在審理的案子
We are considering a case
能直接影響到總統職位
that will directly affect the office of the presidency.
我知道  一個以布雷特參與簽署的重要法案
I know, a case based on the monumental piece of legislation
為基礎的案子
co-signed by Brett.
但我們三個今天碰面
But the three of us standing here right now
跟那無關
have nothing to do with that.
對不對  議員
Isn't that right, Congressman?
對  總統女士
Yes, Madam President.
我會讓議長解釋的
I'll let the speaker explain.
因為有幾項選擇供你考慮
'Cause you have a number of options to consider.
我想讓你知道這件事讓我多尷尬
And I want you to know how truly embarrassing it is for me.
我為最高法院選的人竟要面對如此悲哀的命運
The sad fate of my choice for the court.
另外  我愛尚普蘭湖
And by the way, I love Lake Champlain.
我只去過兩次
I've only been there twice,
但我永遠忘不了湖水濺在腳上的冰冷
but I'll never forget the thrilling shock
是多刻骨銘心
of the cold water on my feet.
我孫子得了多發性硬化癥  他必須游泳
My grandson has MS. He needs to swim.
我不妄作評論  阿布佐法官
I don't judge, Justice Abruzzo.
不對  除了對謊話
I'll correct that. Except for mendacity.
我沒法支持謊話
That I can't support.
還有  布雷特  你跟謝潑德兄妹匯報時
And, Brett, when you report this back to the Shepherds,
替我代好
give them my best.
作為謝潑德家族的一員  你知道自己有責任
As a Shepherd, you know it's your duty to
回報藝術事業  回報你所在的社區
give back to the arts and the communities you're involved in.
我們在加德納分析做的一切
You know, everything we've ever done at Gardner Analytics
都是為了服務用戶
is to serve the user.
你已經說的很清楚了  沒錯
You've made that clear, yes.
但你知道用戶授權給了你們
And yet, you were aware of the amount of data
多少數據
the user was essentially signing over to you.
并不比其他應用多
No more than any other application.
但白宮聲稱
But the White House is saying
謝潑德自由基金會應用
that the Shepherd Freedom Foundation app
比其他應用更過分
went beyond any other application.
它讓國會競選團隊
That it allowed congressional campaigns
獲得用戶手機的全部權限
complete access to the user's phone.
有人甚至說
Some are even saying that
這款應用能操控人的精神
the app is essentially mining peoples' psyches.
是這樣
Look.
我們設計了應用
You design the thing, but at the end of the day,
但無從知道人們會怎么使用它
you have no idea how it will be used.
謝潑德先生
Mr. Shepherd.
我能失陪一下嗎
Could you excuse me for one moment, please?
我是聯調局的斯雷特探員
I'm Agent Slater with the FBI.
有什么事嗎
What's this about?
請跟我們來一趟
Please come with us.
在通知律師之前我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere until I call my lawyer.
謝潑德先生  請吧
Mr. Shepherd, please.
你最好配合一點
It'd be best if you cooperated.
阿布魯佐正申請回避
Abruzzo is recusing himself.
為什么
On what grounds?
利益沖突
His conflict of interest.
這可事關總統之位的未來
This is about the future of the presidency.
他用自己在部隊服役的事當借口
He's using his military service.
把他叫過來
Get him over here.
太遲了  他不能撤回申請了
It's too late, he can't reverse himself.
遲不遲由我來定
I decide when it's too late.
我不會讓這個裁決通過的
I will not have that ruling upheld.
我們還能去找誰
Who else can we get to?
巴里
Barry.
安奈特  別開電視
Annette, do not turn on the TV.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
他們把他帶走了  他們帶著逮捕證闖了進來
They took him. They came in with a warrant.
你說他被帶走了是什么意思
What do you mean they took him?
他們以應用為由
They're using his work with the app
控訴他犯有叛國罪
as grounds to charge him with treason.
我向你保證  我們會極盡所能去救他
I promise you, we will do everything we can.
但所有與這款應用有牽連的人
But anyone connected with the app
都在和它  還有你撇清關系
is distancing themselves from it and you.
這一刻終于來了
It's finally here.
稿子都是誰改的
Where did these changes come from?
謝潑德家族直接改的
Directly from the Shepherd family.
是他媽媽嗎
His mother?
只管做好你的工作  開始錄像吧
Look, just do your thing. Let's get it on tape.
納粹一般的策略
Nazi-like tactics?
除非話題有關二戰
You bring up Nazis in any situation
不然你一提起納粹
other than the Second World War,
就已經輸掉辯論了
you've already lost the argument.
得了吧  我們都知道鄧肯干了什么
I mean, come on, we all knew what Duncan was doing.
還有誰沒料到嗎
Is anybody really surprised?
-認真的嗎  -梅樂蒂
- I mean, really? - Melody...
怎么了
What?
-你這是  -不干了
- What are you-- - No.
民調顯示她的支持率達75%以上
She's polling in the high 70s.
到中期選舉時可能達到近80%
We're looking at close to 80 by the midterms.
反企業浪潮
The anti-corporate rant
也在愈演愈烈
is gaining traction.
她在拿女權主義當武器
She's weaponized her feminism,
這讓人越來越厭煩
and it's grown tiresome.
"我是個母親  也是個將軍"
"I'm a mother, I'm a general."
拉倒吧
Spare me.
像她這么受歡迎的人對民主是有害的
Anyone that popular is bad for democracy.
馬克
Mark.
先說有利之處
So, the pros.
她死后  副總統的位子空缺
After her death, with the vice presidency vacant,
我們的朋友布雷特·柯爾會成為總統
our friend Brett Cole will be president.
我們猜想到時人們會呼吁安定和團結
We suspect we'll get a call for stability and unity.
治愈這個國家  套路大家都清楚
Heal the nation, we all know the drill.
不利之處是  我們會在中期選舉受到打擊
The cons. We're gonna take a hit in the midterms.
我覺得眾議院還能保住
I think we hold on to the House.
參議院就難說了
The Senate is a long shot.
市場會波動一段時間
The markets will fluctuate for a while.
為此我叫了洛琳來
I've brought Lorraine in for that.
她做了一些很不錯的
She's got some impressive
計算機模型和預測
computer models and projections. But...
總而言之  我們有信心承受
all in all, we're confident we can absorb
刺殺所能引發的
whatever financial hit
經濟波動所導致的金融損失
an assassination would have on the economy.
GDP總值可能最多會損失
We're talking about a quarter point loss
四分之一個百分點
in the GDP, at the most.
那可能引發的陰謀論呢
And what about all the conspiracy nonsense we'll be hearing?
這些論調可以分散人們的注意力
The theories are a useful distraction.
最終都會不了了之
And eventually, they consume themselves.
這在歷史上有先例可循
History will back us up on that.
還有個重大的障礙
There's one hiccup. It's a big one.
她懷了孩子
She's with child.
這是一個我們不知道如何
That is a variable we don't know
在我們的模型中計算或預測的變量
how to account for in our models or predict.
我們要利用它
We use it. Play into it.
我們要讓她成為烈士
We'll make her a martyr.
時代的犧牲品
A victim of the times.
女權主義的偶像
A feminist icon.
天哪  她甚至可能被印到硬幣上
God, she might even end up on a coin.
意外拍攝到肯尼迪被刺殺場景的路人
只要不再出現一個澤普魯德
As long as another Zapruder doesn't show up.
杰克  這不好笑
Jack, that's not funny.
我想知道的就這么多
Well, that's as much as I want to know.
是的  我想你們最好現在就走吧
Yes, I think it's best if you all leave now.
接下來交給我
I'll take it from here.
把他帶進來
Bring him in.
到最后關頭了
It's 11 o'clock, as they say.
你想要我手里的東西
You want what I have.
事實上  我希望你繼續拿著
Actually, I want you to hold on to it.
我告訴過賽斯  我再告訴你一次
I told Seth, and I'll tell you again.
我想把她搞垮  而不是弗蘭西斯
I want to bring her down, but not Francis.
難道你不知道那是不可能的嗎
Don't you know that's impossible?
即使殺她丈夫的人就是她
Even if she killed her husband?
道格...
Doug...
我們兩個的目標是一致的
my goal and yours have become the same.
她叫你道格嗎
Does she call you Doug?
還是像她叫弗蘭西斯一樣
Or does she do that Francis thing of hers.
道格拉斯
Douglas.
你知道我們需要做什么
You know what we need to do.
你總是把我想錯
You keep mistaking me for someone I'm not.
我不在乎你  也不在乎你想要什么
I don't care about you or what you want.
但你確實在乎弗蘭克想要什么
But you do care what Frank wanted.
現在你該承認了
And it's time you admitted it.
弗蘭克想讓她死
Frank wanted her dead.
這對你來說似乎更像是私人恩怨
This seems too personal for you.
所有政治都是私人恩怨
All politics is personal.
你是最該知道這一點的人
You of all people know that.
你也希望她死
And you want her dead, too.
我們兩個人都不能單獨做成這件事
And neither one of us can do it alone.
你很快就會想明白的
You'll come to your senses soon.
你不是傻瓜
You're no fool.
你想保護他留給你的東西嗎
You want to protect what he left you?
這是唯一的辦法
It's the only way.
我要為法院即將做出的判決祝賀你
Congratulations on the ruling coming out of the court.
他們還沒有決定
They still haven't decided.
但我們都知道結果會如何
But we all know how it's going to go.
請坐
Please, sit down.
諾拉·卡弗蒂...
Nora Cafferty...
有一個秘密
has a secret.
您說什么
Excuse me.
我以為你是在擔心胎兒的事
I assume you were worried about the scare with the baby.
我跟佩特羅夫總統談過
I spoke to President Petrov.
他告訴我
He's informed me that
哈里發國正在試圖獲取核設備
ICO is trying to acquire a nuclear device.
對  確實
Yes. They are.
那你為什么沒告訴我
So why didn't you tell me?
我完全信任你  諾拉
I have full confidence in you, Nora,
也信任你的能力  但這讓我擔心
and your abilities, but this concerns me.
你在任何情況下都不能
You cannot under any circumstances
隱瞞對我們國家安全至關重要的信息
withhold information that is essential to our national security.
我曾對你有很高的期待
I had such high hopes for you.
你說什么
I'm sorry.
我本不想把這話說出來
I didn't want to have to say this.
我本希望最高法院的判決對你不利
I was hoping the Supreme Court would rule against you.
希望他們剝奪你控制核武的權利
That they would take away the football.
我不是唯一一個開始有這種感覺的人
And I'm not the only one who's starting to feel it.
這是我的地盤  我要你出去
This is my house, and I want you out.
她準備要譴責她丈夫了
She's ready to condemn her husband.
那你為什么不那樣做呢
So why aren't you?
殺死湯姆的不是小偷
It wasn't a thief who killed Tom.
不是
No.
我覺得不是
I don't think it was.
聽著  我和湯姆當時在...
Look, Tom and I were working on--
得了  我知道他在干什么
Okay, I know what he was working on.
我花了將近一個月才找到
It took me almost a month to find it,
但那東西在狗的項圈上
but it was on his dog's collar.
他做的事情跟
It was the same thing
盧卡斯和之前佐伊做的事一樣
Lucas was working on and Zoe before that.
總是遇到同樣的問題
Always with the same problem,
沒有人肯相信
no one will believe it.
-我都跟他說了  -沒有任何證據
- Look, I laid it out for him-- - Without any evidence.
難道你有證據嗎
Or do you have any?
全都是你的說辭
All there is, is your word.
現在那還有什么價值
And what is that even worth these days?
你到底在保護什么
I mean, what the hell are you protecting?
我可以繼續開  沒關系的
I can keep driving. I don't mind.
或者你可以幫我完成湯姆  盧卡斯
Or you can help me finish the story of Tom, Lucas,
佐伊  你  還有...
Zoe, you and...
也許還有我的報道
maybe me.
我試探了你
I tested you.
你通過了
And you passed.
我就是這么看的  總統女士
That's basically how I see it, Madam President.
你好無禮
You're impertinent.
從一開始就特別明顯
That was clear from the start.
不  我有野心
No, I'm ambitious.
我一直都很敬佩你的野心
Which is something that I've always admired,
哪怕我在遠處
from afar, about you.
你攻擊我也是出于敬佩嗎
Even when you were attacking me?
原諒我  我緊張的時候會咄咄逼人
Forgive me. I become aggressive when I'm nervous.
老毛病了
It's always been that way.
我們可以重新來過嗎
Can we start over?
因為我好像終于理解了你
Because I think I finally understand you
理解了你想為這個國家做的
and what you're trying to do for this country.
我可以當你的傳聲筒
I can help you get your message out.
好啊
Sure.
-好了  準備好  各位  -開始吧
- All right, settle, people. - Okay, let's begin.
四  三  二...
Let's go in four, three, two--
首先
First things first.
不管賭局猜是哪種性別
Despite what the odds-makers have decided,
是個女孩  我就要當媽媽了
I am going to be the mother of a baby girl.
-恭喜  -謝謝
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
你想好給她取什么名字了嗎
And have you picked out a name?
還沒有
Um, not yet.
我得先見到她的小臉
I need to see her face first.
你最希望美國人民了解你的哪一點
What do you most wish the American people knew about you?
出人意料的一面
Something surprising.
我最喜歡大笑了
That I like nothing more than to laugh.
即將成為母親
And what does the prospect of becoming a mother,
同時又是自由世界的領導  是什么感覺
while being the leader of the free world, feel like?
苦中帶甜
Bittersweet.
我當然沒想過會以遺孀的身份生下弗蘭西斯的孩子
I didn't expect to deliver Francis' child as a widow, of course.
但我有責任要盡  為了我尚未出世的孩子
But I have things to do for my unborn child,
為了這個不成熟的國家
for this unformed nation.
我想創造出進步而高效的黑爾政治遺產
I want to create a progressive and productive Hale legacy
并影響后世
for the ages.
說到這點
Speaking of which.
你為什么重新用娘家姓了
Why did you return to your maiden name?
答案就在你的問題里
Well, I think your question answered itself.
娘家姓[少女名]
Maiden name.
這種稱呼的背后含義
The assumptions behind that expression
讓我回歸了我的本名
led me back to what I can only call my name.
黑爾總統
President Hale,
為什么副總統空缺
why the delay in nominating a replacement
遲遲不做提名
for the vice presidential vacancy?
有兩個原因  其一  是因為憲法
Two reasons. One, constitutionally,
要求國會確認人選
Congress needs to confirm the choice
但現在  國會烏煙瘴氣
and our current Congress is dirty.
我們得看中期選舉的結果
We'll have to see what happens with the midterms.
其二  要說我從搭檔關系中學到了什么
And two, if I've learned anything from partnerships,
你必須選一個甘愿為你擋子彈的人
you have to choose someone who'd take a bullet for you.
還有  梅樂蒂  有件事我想澄清一下
And, Melody, I'd like to come clean on something.
請講
Please.
真相是  雖然說出真相讓我很痛苦
The truth is, and it pains me to say this,
但真相是  這個國家
but the truth is, this country
從未有機會了解真正的弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
never got to know the real Francis Underwood.
連我自己都未必真了解他
I'm not sure I ever really knew him myself.
我知道你也看出來了
I know you saw it, too.
他無法被看透  就跟其他騙子一樣
He was impossible to know, like all con men.
他把我們都耍了
He played us all.
來找我啊  道格
Come and get me, Doug.
她讓我別無選擇
She leaves me no choice.
*劃呀劃  劃小船*
*Row, row, row your boat*
*順溪流  緩緩流*
*Gently down the stream*
*多歡樂  多歡樂*
*Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily*
*人生是夢一場*
*Life is but a dream*
*劃呀劃  劃小船  順溪流  緩緩流*
*Row, row, row your boat gently down the stream*
*瞧見鱷魚*
*If you see a crocodile*
*記得叫喊*
*Don't forget to scream*
"核武橄欖球"可追溯到冷戰時期  在核戰爭一觸即發的形勢下
美國總統出行時開始攜帶可以下令發動核武攻擊的"核按鈕"
但其實  "橄欖球"是一個標準的Zero Halliburton牌鋁制保險箱
外套一個黑皮公文包
箱內主要物品是總統考慮發動核打擊時的打擊方案  啟動警報的程序
以及最重要的  一個印有密碼的塑料卡片  用來驗證總統身份
這個卡片被叫做"餅干"
利用包內的物品  美國總統可以同五角大樓的指揮中心聯系
在驗證身份后  下令實施核打擊
總統出行時  "橄欖球"由一名經過最嚴格背景調查的武官攜帶保管
這名武官被要求必須時刻緊跟總統左右  但也會有意外情況發生
里根總統遇刺后  被專車迅速送往醫院進行緊急手術
而攜帶"橄欖球"的武官卻沒有立刻隨車前往
事后人們還發現  里根當時把帶有驗證碼的"餅干"放在了自己的襪子里
而手術期間這個可以發動核戰爭的塑料卡片被護士丟在了醫院的地板上
在美國的媒體江湖中  絕大部分的主流媒體
如《紐約時報》《華盛頓郵報》《時代周刊》
NBC  CBS  ABC三大電視網  CNN  MSNBC等有線新聞臺
都在意識形態上不同程度左傾  偏向民主黨  對民主黨政客也呵護有加
只有《華爾街日報》和福克斯新聞網是共和黨的盟友
但正因為右派媒體少  所以支持共和黨的民眾都集中在這兩家媒體
再加上經營有方  福克斯新聞和《華爾街日報》都在同行競爭中占優勢
而這兩家媒體的老板是同一個人  新聞集團的主席默多克
在巨大的受眾群體的支持下  這兩家媒體在政治輿論戰中舉足輕重
默多克家族在美國政壇自然也影響巨大  呼風喚雨
奧巴馬執政期間  福克斯新聞對民主黨政府一直苛責不斷
而特朗普上臺后  福克斯新聞則成了新政府最好的朋友
特朗普在競選期間  就經常找默多克商量競選事宜
搬入白宮后  也經常給默多克打電話咨詢政務  還常邊看福克斯新聞邊發推特
以至于全美國關心政治的媒體公眾也跟著成了福克斯新聞的觀眾
福克斯的一些主持人在默多克的默許下  成為特朗普的親密戰友
在節目中夸贊新政府的豐功偉績  攻擊起特朗普的政敵則毫不留情